Tripman
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I am off to school!!
Oh no, I'm late!
Watch where you're going!
But you were the one who bumped into me!
I have no time for this!
I'm so late!
You were late?
It's all your fault.
If you woke up earlier, you wouldn't be late.
You would have made it in time!
Easy for you to say, If I wasn’t being pushed down by Giant...
I would've been able to make it in time.
It's very frustrating!
You sure are helpless, let's try this Tripman.
Koroshiya
A hitman?
No, not professional killer.
I said he's not hitman....
but rather he's a Tripman.
Korubashiya
I see! I was scared for life!
But what's a Tripman, anyway?
Like his name suggests, he wrestles people and knocks them down.
Just put ¥10 into the opening in its' back.
And call a name of someone, whom you hate!
It may sound boring...
But he's great gadget for payback to Giant.
Alright, I'll hire Tripman with ¥10.
Let's give Giant a hard time!
What now?
He is a pro.
He will trip Giant 3 times.
I wanna see him in action!
He walks like an expert.
I wonder if he knows where Giant is.
What the hell are you?
Damn you little punk, trying to give me a hard time!
You should know your place! I'll tear you into pieces!
Ouch!
Go away, stay away from me!
Great!
Help!
Stop!
I'm sorry.
Please!
He is quite a pro, alright!
He is bloodless and tearless wrestler!
Alright, from now on, I am going to use this!
to teach a lesson to those people who are trying to give me a hard time!
I got you!
Ouch!
How dare you do that to me? Just watch me now!
Let me show you my Tripman!
Nobita-kun!
What's up?
Don't call my name now!
No, it's not me!
Mr. Cop!
Help me!
Doraemon!
Oh boy, I outran the Tripman at last!
What happened, why are you like this?
I had a hard time. Actually...
No!
Once Tripman gets a request, he'll be sure to see through the request.
Oh no! What am I supposed to do now?!
Put ¥100 in and he will reject the request.
No kidding! I have spent ¥20 already!
So you have no other choice but to be trip.
Yes?
Who is there?
Do it, I have ¥100.
Go cancel it!
Count on me!
I'm coming!
Please don't tear my house down.
I'll go and see!
Cancel the deal!
It's safe for you to come out now.
I have canceled the deal.
I spent ¥120, what a deal!
I canceled it, but why did you trip down?